宝宝好
今天周五呢要不要我们喝一点
微醺很适合放松呢
宝宝你工作一周哦
我也想给你放松放松啊
来宝宝干杯
你还记不记得我们是怎么认识的
对就在图书馆呵
你当时还跟我玩拉扯
我也就看着你自己在那边纠结犹豫
最后还是忍不住主动问我要联系方式呢
♪ I see you ♪
♪ But you don't see me ♪
♪ It's so obvious ♪
Why you say they just want something out of everything
That should that the judo for every p
♪ I just wishing you would say the truth ♪
Bly as i
你还想狡辩什么呢
放弃抵抗吧
你就是要在我这儿乖乖的对啊
没办法
我的温柔一点点的让你放下架子
怪谁啊
♪ I've been so lately ♪
♪ Cause ♪
♪ I'm a ♪
当然不会嫌弃你啊
就算是玩也是训你的时候玩的
怎么了怎么了
♪ Found love ♪
♪ And i'm so ♪
你总是说你喜欢凶的
可是我就是你的温柔主啊
我舍不得凶你啊
再说了
你那么可爱
dream会心动呢
♪ Taso sweet ♪
而你呢不知道什么好
真是的
Life could be so n
训你的时候
我对你很腼腆
你会不会更喜欢我呢
Love me life is
but真的
The train and the time so sweet
Tf
Baby just love your life
Could be cream
And it's all a dream tonight
对
你必须守我的规矩
要你伸手
你就把手伸出来
我的乖宝哼哼啊
真乖呢
最喜欢你啦
宝宝你喜不喜欢我训你呀
Life could
喜欢啊
看把你激动的和决给你留下我专属的标记
好不好嗯
怕怕疼啊
宝宝
啊
烫不烫啊
看着你这一副享受的样子
You see me
It's so obvious
♪ Why everybody comes out on the same day ♪
I just want something out of everything
Isn't that they objection of every time
I just swishing
♪ You would see the truth ♪
They're not everybody is not there to get you
♪ Then not everything has to be some dark blue ♪
♪ Your melancholy serves as ♪